The TechNet module repository is a nifty thing.  It provides thousands of scripts that are available to anyone, and has become a great one-stop-shop for finding community modules.


It's also a giant pain to automate.


I've produced a pretty substantial number of [modules](http://start-automating.com/Modules) over the years, but only started publishing to Technet recently.  Why?  Because I didn't have the right tools.  


The TechNet Tools module includes and relies upon [PowerShell Pipeworks](http://powershellpipeworks.com) and [AutoBrowse](http://autobrowse.start-automating.com).  It allows you to automate publishing modules to TechNet, check your technet stats, and check your contributions.  I hope it helps you publish cool tools to TechNet.
